so the multi-level page table still
looks at the virtual address in terms of
page offset and page number but instead
of using the entire page number to
Access one huge table it partitions the
page number into the so-called inner
page number and the outer page number
the outer page number tells us which
part of the large pay table we would be
using the inner part tells us which
specific entry in that large page table
we would be using instead of having the
large page table the outer page number
is now used to index into the outer page
table and each entry in the outer page
table tells us where to find the
so-called inner page table once we find
the inner page table we take the inner
page number and use it to index into the
inner page table and what we find there
is the actual frame number to AIS
another entry in the outer page page
table will point to a different inner
page table so pretty much what we have
is the outer page number tells us which
of the small inner page tables to use
and the inner page number tells us where
in each of the page tables we need to
look at so it seems like this is just a
more complicated way to access the page
table but still for every possible page
number we will have a frame number in
one of the inner page tables the total
size of the inner page tables will be
the size of the original flat page table
and we still have added the outer page
table which we didn't have before so
pretty much we still have the same
number of entries total here and we have
added something so where are the savings